United Steelworkers of America Records of Local 1010 (Inland Steel Co.) Arbitration Awards and Related Documents 5980
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Steelworkers of America Records of Local 1010 (Inland Steel Co.) Arbitration Awards and Related Documents
1983-1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Steelworkers of America (USWA)
USWA Local 1010
5980
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5745659
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 17, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Iron and steel workers -- Labor unions--Indiana--East Chicago; Collective bargaining--Steel industry--Indiana--East Chicago; United Steelworkers of America.; Inland Steel Company; United Steelworkers of America. Local 1010 (East Chicago, Ind.)
5745659
- Index to Awards of Permanent Arbitrators (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Inter-Communication - Inland Steel (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Area No. 9 Griever - Rob Persons (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Plant Policy Committee (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Frozen Incentives (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Local Union 1010 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- The Historical Development of Three Chicago Millgates (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Basic Steel Agreement, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Inequity Program (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Gainshare Information (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Calculation Guideline (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Total of Proposed Protected Craft Employees (Box 1, Folder 12)
- BOF/CC (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Miriam Balanoff (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Department Presentation (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Misc. Documents (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Joint Committee - Grievance Procedure (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Wages/ Incentives (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Grievance Procedure (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Local Working Conditions (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Overtime & Scheduling (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Rank & File - Printing Bills Election, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Crew Site Arbs (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Steelyard Blues (Box 1, Folder 24)
- LMRC Notes (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Steelabor (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Settlement Agreement, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Local 1010 Steelworker (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Foreign Awards (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Opinion & Award (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Base Rate Arbitrations (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Inland Mini-Arb (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Contracting Out (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Arbitration 738-747 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Arbitration 714-737 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Arbitration 748-767 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Arbitration 768- (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Arbitration Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Grievances (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Old Papers - Rough Drafts (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Arbitrations 600-632 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Arbitrations 667-679 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Arbitrations 654-665 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Arbitrations 646-653 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Arbitrations 634-645 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Arbitrations 680-695 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Arbitrations 700-713 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Arbitrations 208-393 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Arbitrations 414-596 (Box 3, Folder 12)